Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Cancer Center, 1972 -- 1985; MS224.003; 4.8 Linear Feet
  - Office of Cancer Control - Cancer Center Institute, 1972 -- 1985; MS224.003.002
    - Cancer Center/Institute Bulletin, 1981 -- 1983; MS224.003.019.00003 (Box 19)
      Office of Cancer Control - Cancer Center Institute. Non-consecutive. 4 issues.
    - Cancer Center/Institute Bulletin correspondence, 1980 -- 1981; MS224.003.019.00004 (Box 19)
    - Cancer Center/Institute Committees: Executive, External Advisory, Finance Committees, 1982 -- 1983; MS224.003.019.00005 (Box 19)
    - Cancer Control office, 1976 -- 1978; MS224.003.019.00006 (Box 19)
    - Cancer Plan for the 80's, 1981; MS224.003.019.00007; Marchant, Douglas J. (Box 19)
    - Charge back issue, 1981 -- 1983; MS224.003.019.00008 (Box 19)
    - Committee membership lists, 1983; MS224.003.019.00009 (Box 19)
    - Core Grant/Cancer Institute correspondence, 1979; MS224.003.019.00010 (Box 19)
    - Core Grant/Cancer Institute correspondence, 1980; MS224.003.019.00011 (Box 19)
    - Core Grant/Cancer Institute correspondence, 1981; MS224.003.019.00012 (Box 19)
    - Core Grant/Cancer Institute correspondence, 1982; MS224.003.019.00013 (Box 19)
    - Core Grant/Cancer Institute correspondence, 1983; MS224.003.019.00014 (Box 19)
    - Core Grant/Cancer Institute correspondence, 1984 -- 1985; MS224.003.019.00015 (Box 19)
    - Developmental funds proposals, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.003.019.00016 (Box 19)
    - Developmental funds proposals, 1980; MS224.003.019.00017 (Box 19)
    - Drug roster of the NEMCH, MS224.003.019.00018 (Box 19)
    - Equipment inventory, 1979 -- 1983; MS224.003.019.00019 (Box 19)
    - Financial projections, 1982; MS224.003.019.00020 (Box 19)
    - Grant application: Study of the use of steroid hormone receptors in the management of patients with endometrial, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.003.019.00021 (Box 19)
    - Membership handbook, MS224.003.019.00022 (Box 19)
    - Membership lists, 1983; MS224.003.019.00023 (Box 19)
    - Organization charts showing evolution of center, 1979 -- 1982; MS224.003.019.00024 (Box 19)
    - Support letters - Drs. Grossman and Levy, 1982 -- 1983; MS224.003.019.00025 (Box 19)
    - Tufts Cancer Research Center dedication - Tufts Medical Alumni Bulletin, 1972; MS224.003.019.00026 (Box 19)
      Office of Cancer Control - Cancer Center Institute. Volume 31, no. 3., pages 3-10.
    - Tufts Health Science Review, 1977; MS224.003.019.00027 (Box 19)
    - Cancer Center guidelines for review of Cancer Center support (core) grants, 1982; MS224.003.019.00028 (Box 19)
    - Core grant critique correspondence, 1983; MS224.003.019.00029 (Box 19)
    - Core grant critique, 1978; MS224.003.019.00030 (Box 19)
    - Core grant critique, 1982; MS224.003.019.00031 (Box 19)
    - Core grant critique, 1983; MS224.003.019.00032 (Box 19)
    - Core grant proposal, 1977; MS224.003.019.00033 (Box 19)
    - Core grant progress report, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.003.019.00034 (Box 19)
    - Core grant progress report, 1980 -- 1981; MS224.003.019.00035 (Box 19)
    - Core grant progress report, 1984; MS224.003.019.00036 (Box 19)
    - Core grant competitive renewal, 1982; MS224.003.020.00001 (Box 20)
    - Critique core grant proposal, 1976; MS224.003.020.00002 (Box 20)
    - Renewal, core grant proposal, 1981; MS224.003.020.00003 (Box 20)
    - Site visit briefing book, 1983; MS224.003.020.00004 (Box 20)
    - Site visit preparation materials, 1978; MS224.003.020.00005 (Box 20)
    - Site visit preparation materials, 1981; MS224.003.020.00006 (Box 20)
    - Site visit preparation materials, 1983; MS224.003.020.00007 (Box 20)
    - Site visitors packet, 1983; MS224.003.020.00008 (Box 20)
    - T-NEMC operating account budget, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.003.020.00009 (Box 20)
    - T-NEMC operating account budget, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.003.020.00010 (Box 20)
    - T-NEMC operating account budget, 1980 -- 1981; MS224.003.020.00011 (Box 20)
    - T-NEMC operating account budget, 1981 -- 1982; MS224.003.020.00012 (Box 20)
    - T-NEMC operating account budget, 1982 -- 1983; MS224.003.020.00013 (Box 20)
    - T-NEMC operating account budget, 1983 -- 1984; MS224.003.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - Monthly department budget report review, 1985; MS224.003.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - T-NEMC Free Fund budget, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.003.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - T-NEMC Free Fund budget, 1980 -- 1981; MS224.003.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - T-NEMC Free Fund budget, 1981 -- 1982; MS224.003.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - Goode, Shiela, 1983 -- 1984; MS224.003.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Raam, Shanthi, 1982; MS224.003.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - Dana Farber Cancer Control Program/Sidney Farber Cancer Control Program, 1976 -- 1984; MS224.003.003
    - Cancer Control guidelines, 1982 -- 1983; MS224.003.021.00008 (Box 21)
      Dana Farber Cancer Control Program/Sidney Farber Cancer Control Program
    - Cancer Institute Bulletin and membership handbook, 1983; MS224.003.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Communications Advisory Committee progress report, 1982 -- 1983; MS224.003.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - Grant Proposal, 1977 -- 1980; MS224.003.021.00011 (Box 21)
    - Grant Proposal - program for regional cancer control volume 1, 1979; MS224.003.021.00012 (Box 21)
    - Grant Proposal - program for regional cancer control volume 2, 1979; MS224.003.021.00013 (Box 21)
    - Guide to Smoking Prevention Education Resources for Schools, 1980; MS224.003.021.00014 (Box 21)
    - Hospice Subcommittee, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.003.021.00015; Regional Cancer Control Committee Sidney Farber Cancer Institute (Box 21)
    - Hospice: A Massachusetts Perspective, 1980; MS224.003.021.00016; Regional Cancer Control Committee Sidney Farber Cancer Institute (Box 21)
    - Primary Breast Cancer: Recommendations for Diagnosis and Treatment, 1980; MS224.003.021.00017; Regional Cancer Control Committee Sidney Farber Cancer Institute (Box 21)
    - Regional Cancer Control Committee Breast Cancer Subcommittee, 1978 -- 1980; MS224.003.021.00018 (Box 21)
    - Regional Cancer Control hospital discharge study, MS224.003.021.00019 (Box 21)
    - Sidney Farber Cancer Control Center grant progress report, 1981 -- 1984; MS224.003.021.00020 (Box 21)
    - Smoking Cessation Program, 1978 -- 1981; MS224.003.021.00021 (Box 21)
    - Surgical management of breast disease, 1979-11; MS224.003.021.00022 (Box 21)
      Dana Farber Cancer Control Program/Sidney Farber Cancer Control Program. "Something About Everything," Jorge Tello, MD
    - Tufts/BU Regional Cancer Program (Precursor to regional program), 1976; MS224.003.021.00023 (Box 21)
- Financial records, 1969 -- 1981; MS224.004; 9.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains the budget and accounting information of T-NEMC administration, as well as research initiatives undertaken at T-NEMC. Records in this series include grant applications, contracts, and their associated files. There is a large body of correspondence and memos.
  Personnel information is restricted.
  Records of General Accounting may be found in boxes 22 and 23. Within the Research Accounting group, records of the Associated Health Professions Educational Development Project may be found in boxes 24, 25, and 47 and Grant and Contract Files may be found in boxes 26-28.
  - Properties fund general ledger, 1971; MS224.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
    Records of General Accounting
  - Operating fund general ledger, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.004.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Operating and properties funds final general ledger, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.004.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Operating fund general ledger, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.004.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Properties fund general ledger, 1972; MS224.004.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Properties fund general ledger, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.004.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Properties fund general ledger, 1975; MS224.004.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Operating fund general ledger, 1975; MS224.004.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Expenses Year 4, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.004.023.00002 (Box 23)
    Records of Research Account. Records of Associated Health Professions Education Project, 1976-1981
  - Proedures for the Establishment and Renewal of Clinical Affiliation Agreements, 1980; MS224.004.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Office Procedures, 1980; MS224.004.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Graduate Programs - Allied Health, 1980; MS224.004.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Contract Development, 1980; MS224.004.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Contract development training meeting, 1980; MS224.004.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Associated health project planning, 1976 -- 1978; MS224.004.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Statewide planning for allied health education - Mrs. Joan Pinck, 1978; MS224.004.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - Coordinated dietetic internship, 1977; MS224.004.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - Cytotechnologist, 1977; MS224.004.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - Community mental health, 1977; MS224.004.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - Clinical Pathology, 1977; MS224.004.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - NEMCH - Clinical Chemistry Laboratory, 1978; MS224.004.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - Child Psychiatry Service, 1977; MS224.004.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - Chemistry Technician, MS224.004.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Blood bank technician, 1977; MS224.004.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - Associated health expenses - miscellaneous items, 1977 -- 1979; MS224.004.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Memos, correspondence, meeting notes, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.004.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence - Berliner, Richard (personal), 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - AHPED: reading file correspondence, 1979; MS224.004.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Associated health project correspondence, 1979; MS224.004.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, 1980 -- 1981; MS224.004.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Associated health project "Expanded Duties for Dental Auxiliaries" training grant, 1977; MS224.004.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - Biomedical engineering, resources - "How to Educate Clinical Engineers - The Internship Approach", 1977; MS224.004.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Biomedical engineering technician, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Bacteriology: MTL-ASCP, 1977; MS224.004.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Animal technician, 1977; MS224.004.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Boston school of occupational therapy, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Associated helath project planning (miscellaneous), 1971 -- 1976; MS224.004.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - T-NEMC allied health survey, 1980; MS224.004.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Responses, T-NEMC allied health survey, 1980; MS224.004.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Associated health project correspondence, 1977; MS224.004.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - AHPED correspondence, 1980; MS224.004.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Reports, 1975 -- 1979; MS224.004.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Grant application, "Training in Emergency Medical Services", 1979 -- 1980; MS224.004.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, 1979; MS224.004.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Associated health project, "Factors Affecting Career Mobility", 1978; MS224.004.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - AmaraSingham, Saha, 1977; MS224.004.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - chronological file, 1978; MS224.004.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - Dental assistant, 1977; MS224.004.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Dental auxilary programs, MS224.004.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Dental continuing education, 1977; MS224.004.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - Dental hygenists, MS224.004.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - Dietary technician, 1977; MS224.004.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Dietetic clinical experience, 1977; MS224.004.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Dietetic traineeship, MS224.004.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - Family support, 1977; MS224.004.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Medical continuing education, 1977; MS224.004.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - Medical records administrator, 1977; MS224.004.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Medical records technician, 1977; MS224.004.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Medical rehabilitation, MS224.004.024.00017 (Box 24)
    Records of Research Account. Records of Associated Health Professions Education Project, 1976-1981. Folder is empty.
  - Medical technologist, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.004.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Nuclear medicine technologist, 1969 -- 1977; MS224.004.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - NEMCH: Nurse anesthetist program, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Nurse's aide, MS224.004.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - Nurse practitioner program, 1977; MS224.004.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - Nurse technician, 1977; MS224.004.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - Nursing affiliation, 1977; MS224.004.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Occupational therapy - affiliation, 1977; MS224.004.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - Pharmacy clinical clerkship, 1977; MS224.004.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - Pharmacy hospital residency, 1975; MS224.004.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - Pharmacy technician, MS224.004.024.00028 (Box 24)
  - Physical therapy - affiliation, 1977; MS224.004.024.00029 (Box 24)
  - Pulmonary function laboratory, 1977; MS224.004.024.00030 (Box 24)
  - Radiologic technician, 1977; MS224.004.024.00031 (Box 24)
  - Radiopharmacy, 1977; MS224.004.024.00032 (Box 24)
  - Rehabilitation biomedical engineering, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.024.00033 (Box 24)
  - Rehabilitation continuing education, MS224.004.024.00034 (Box 24)
  - Rehabilitation, 1977; MS224.004.024.00035 (Box 24)
  - Respiratory therapy, 1977 -- 1980; MS224.004.024.00036 (Box 24)
  - Social service, 1977; MS224.004.024.00037 (Box 24)
  - Speech and hearing, 1973 -- 1977; MS224.004.024.00038 (Box 24)
  - Surgical (O.R.) technician, 1977; MS224.004.024.00039 (Box 24)
  - Therapeutic radiology, 1977; MS224.004.024.00040 (Box 24)
  - Medical technology program - Northeastern University, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.024.00041 (Box 24)
  - Physician's assistant (NEMCH), 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.024.00042 (Box 24)
  - Physician assistant, proposed master's degree program, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.024.00043 (Box 24)
  - Physician assistant program, 1976 -- 1978; MS224.004.024.00044 (Box 24)
  - Physician assistant - additional reading material (bibliography), MS224.004.024.00045 (Box 24)
  - Medical electronics engineering technical - Franklin Institute, 1978; MS224.004.024.00046 (Box 24)
  - Medical laboratory technician - Northeastern University, 1978; MS224.004.024.00047 (Box 24)
  - Physical therapy - TNEMC, 1979; MS224.004.024.00048 (Box 24)
  - Radiologic technology - Bunker Hill Community College, 1979; MS224.004.024.00049 (Box 24)
  - Proposal - clinical psychology, 1978; MS224.004.024.00050 (Box 24)
  - Tufts University - continuing education, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.024.00051 (Box 24)
  - Continuing education - symposium on aging, MS224.004.024.00052 (Box 24)
  - Educational Media Center, 1979; MS224.004.024.00053 (Box 24)
  - Responses from workshop, 1979; MS224.004.024.00054 (Box 24)
  - Associated health - workshop on health team development, issues in interdisciplinary clinical education, 1978; MS224.004.024.00055 (Box 24)
  - Tufts University undergraduate survey - interest in and perception of health related careers final report, 1979; MS224.004.024.00056 (Box 24)
  - Tufts University undergraduate survey - 25 questionnaires, MS224.004.024.00057 (Box 24)
  - Tufts University undergraduate survey - health professions, 1978; MS224.004.024.00058 (Box 24)
  - Dick - survey information, MS224.004.024.00059 (Box 24)
  - Report - master's degree level health education programs, 1979; MS224.004.024.00060 (Box 24)
  - Personnel changes (administration), 1979 -- 1980; MS224.004.024.00061 (Box 24)
  - Confidential personnel information, 1977 -- 1980; MS224.004.024.00062 (Box 24)
    Records of Research Account. Records of Associated Health Professions Education Project, 1976-1981. Contains personnel files.
  - Resumes, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - General information, MS224.004.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Temporary clerk typist, 1981; MS224.004.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - AHPED: short term research position (cost analysis study), 1979; MS224.004.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Drummond, Dave, 1977; MS224.004.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Educational policy committee, 1977; MS224.004.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Dr. Feldberg, 1977; MS224.004.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Tufts University - government resources, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: administrative staff and medical board members, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Health planning, 1977; MS224.004.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Teaching capacity study - clinical education at NEMCH, 1977; MS224.004.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Teaching capacity study financial information - personnel chart of accounts/confidential, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Clinical assessment - model outline and related general material, 1977 -- 1979; MS224.004.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - Medical electronics engineering technology program background and information, 1978; MS224.004.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - physical therapy (lists and correspondence), 1979; MS224.004.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - physical therapy (program information), 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - physical therapy (completed questionnaires), MS224.004.025.00017 (Box 25)
    Records of Research Account. Records of Associated Health Professions Education Project, 1976-1981. Front of folder reads "confidential."
  - Quality assessment - radiologic technology program (drafts and final report), 1979; MS224.004.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - radiologic technology program (completed questionnaires), MS224.004.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Ad hoc geriatric committee, 1978; MS224.004.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Medical lab technician program (Northeastern University), 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - medical lab technician (draft and final report), 1978; MS224.004.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - medical lab technician (notes and correspondence), 1978; MS224.004.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - medical lab technician (completed questionnaires), MS224.004.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - physical therapy (draft and final report), 1979; MS224.004.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - Letter of inquiry - survey - Tufts affiliated hospitals, 1977; MS224.004.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - Directors of associated hospitals questionnaires, 1977 -- 1979; MS224.004.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC - Randolph, Peter, MS224.004.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - Schroeder, Peter - grants and contracts, MS224.004.025.00029 (Box 25)
  - Weisbaum, Larry - grants, 1977; MS224.004.025.00030 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee meeting, 1977; MS224.004.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - Tufts associated hospitals - background developmental of final chart, MS224.004.025.00032 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee meeting, 1977; MS224.004.025.00033 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC public relations materials (Hank Wilson), 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.025.00034 (Box 25)
  - Organizational chart - Tufts University New England Medical Center, 1976; MS224.004.025.00035 (Box 25)
  - Bradford proposal, MS224.004.025.00036 (Box 25)
  - Dunn, Jack, 1977; MS224.004.025.00037 (Box 25)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.025.00038 (Box 25)
  - McCarthy, Kathryn, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.025.00039 (Box 25)
  - Tufts University Board of Trustees, 1978; MS224.004.025.00040 (Box 25)
  - Annual Report of the President, 1977; MS224.004.025.00041 (Box 25)
  - Quality assessment - radiologic technology program (list and correspondence), 1979; MS224.004.025.00042 (Box 25)
  - Block, Roger, MS224.004.025.00043 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: continuing education programs, 1976; MS224.004.025.00044 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Harrington, Dave, 1978; MS224.004.025.00045 (Box 25)
  - Jacobs, Arthur Health Studies - NEMCH, 1977; MS224.004.025.00046 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Medical clinic, 1977; MS224.004.025.00047 (Box 25)
  - Medical staff appointments, 1977; MS224.004.025.00048 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Nursing, 1977; MS224.004.025.00049 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Nursing school proposal, MS224.004.025.00050 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: organizational chart, 1977; MS224.004.025.00051 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Orthopedics department, 1977; MS224.004.025.00052 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Rehab Training Institute, 1978; MS224.004.025.00053 (Box 25)
  - Trull, David, 1977; MS224.004.025.00054 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC: Bay Cove (Tufts) Mental Health Center, 1977; MS224.004.025.00055 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC: Biomedical engineering, 1977; MS224.004.025.00056 (Box 25)
  - Ehrlich, Edward, 1977; MS224.004.025.00057 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC: fiscal model, MS224.004.025.00058 (Box 25)
  - T-NEMC: job descriptions, 1973 -- 1975; MS224.004.025.00059 (Box 25)
  - NEMCH: Rehabilitation Institute brochure, MS224.004.025.00060 (Box 25)
  - 84737-0, Bowdoin Street Health Center, Spinelli, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.026.00001 (Box 26)
    Records of Research Accounting. Grants and Contracts Files, 1971-1978.
  - 84743-0, Multiple scolorsis, Dr. Randic, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.004.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - 84750-3, Dr. Bloedorn, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - 84751-2, Dr. Bloedorn, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.004.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - 84755-0, Dr. Neurath, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.004.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - 84750-4, Dr. Boedorn, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - 84750-5, Radiotherapy Oncology Center, Dr. Munzenrider, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - 84755-3, Dr. Neurath, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - 84750-6, Radiotherapy Oncology Center, Dr. Piro, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - 84751-3, Dr. Bloedorn, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - 84759-3, American Cancer Society, Dr. Wallach, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - 84759-5, American Cancer Society, Dr. Wallach, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - 84760-0, Permanent Charity Fund, Dr. Field, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.004.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - 84761-0, Cancer Control Development, Dr. Marchant, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - 84755-1, White Cell System, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.004.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - 84755-2, Dr. Neurath, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.004.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - 84777-0, Supply Allowance Fellowship, Dr. Moore, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - 84777-0, Psychiatry HSD Training Staff, Dr. Callahan, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - 84778-0, Insitution Allowance, Dr. Mikkelson, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - 84779-0, Multi-ethnic Training in Mental Health, Dr. Mintz, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - 84780-0/24301-0, Mental Health Consortium, Dr. Morrison, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - 84756-2, Dr. Neurath, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00022 (Box 26)
  - 84757-0, Neutron Beam Project, Dr. Bloedorn and Dr. Neurath, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00023 (Box 26)
  - 84758-0, Commonwealth Fund, Dr. Proger, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.004.026.00024 (Box 26)
  - 84758-1, Commonwealth Fund, Dr. Proger, 1975; MS224.004.026.00025 (Box 26)
  - 84765-0, Dr. Wallach, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00026 (Box 26)
  - 84765-1, Dr. Wallach, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.026.00027 (Box 26)
  - 84765-2, Membrane Biology and Pathology Training, Dr. Wallach, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.026.00028 (Box 26)
  - 84766-0, Schrafft Charitable and Other Contributions, 1970; MS224.004.026.00029 (Box 26)
  - 20150-0, Communicator Fund, Mr. Foulds, 1974; MS224.004.026.00030 (Box 26)
  - 84769-0, Medicolegal Rights of Physically Disabled Persons, Mr. Holzer, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.026.00031 (Box 26)
  - 84773-00, Dr. Ding-Jen-Lee, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00032 (Box 26)
  - 84774-0, Institutional Allowance, Dr. Kwock, 1974; MS224.004.026.00033 (Box 26)
  - 84774, Dr. Kwock, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.026.00034 (Box 26)
  - 84775-0, Institutional Allowance, Dr. Miller, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00035 (Box 26)
  - 84776-0, Institutional Allowance, Dr. Anderson, MS224.004.026.00036 (Box 26)
  - 84780-0, Consortium for Continuing Education in Mental Health, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.026.00037 (Box 26)
  - 84780-1, Consortium on Continuing Education, Dr. Mintz, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00001 (Box 27)